In this fast-paced world, people are often
burdened with various financial and emotional worries.
Furthermore, they lead hectic lives.
These factors make them vulnerable to major medical events,
often
referred to as critical illnesses. Such illnesses and
accidents can have a devastating impact on your life. Such
events, such as an unfortunate
event or even a hospital stay, can
impact a person's ability to meet financial obligations, such as meeting home
or daily expenses. The
IIT policy
helps you during any major or minor illness, major surgery, or if you meet with an accident. The
IIT policy comes with several major benefits,
such as: Cardiac coverage; coverage for 106 surgical procedures;
Cancer rehabilitation benefit;
Multiple payouts for critical illnesses. The plan
covers major and minor critical illnesses. It has a
severity-based payout. It includes
100% for major critical illnesses and 0
% for minor critical illnesses, which are
classified as: Cancer and blood
disorders; Heart and blood vessels; Major organs;
Nervous system  Other Illnesses The best part is
that there is no waiting period between claims
and that's not all. Kashi Plus also offers
optional coverage for 106 surgical procedures.
Payouts based on severity are 100% for major surgeries and
50% for minor surgeries. The plan
also offers Cancer Reduction Benefit.
You will be eligible to claim under this benefit
provided you renew the policy
subject to receiving premium for Cancer and Blood Disorders Bucket and Cancer Reduction Benefit as per Basic Sum Assured at the time of renewal. It is better to stay protected when illnesses are on the rise.
Multiple Pay for Critical Illness Option gives
you coverage up to five critical illnesses.